[
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"4 Cities Have Hosted The Modern Day Summer Olympic Games Name Any 2 (PFE)", "answer":0, "answers":["Los Angeles , London , Paris Or Athens"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"A Silver Fern Is The Emblem Of Which Nations Rugby Union Team?", "answer":0, "answers":["New Zealand"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"A Snooker Player Makes A Break Of Eight Points. Which Three Colours Are Potted? (PFE)", "answer":0, "answers":["Red, Yellow & Brown"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"A Statue Of Billy Bremner Stands Outside The Ground Of Which Football Ground?", "answer":0, "answers":["Leeds United"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"A Yokouna is a grand champion in which sport?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sumo"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"According To A Survey Conducted In 2000 Which 2 People Were Voted The Greatest Male & Female Tennis Players Of All Time Respectively?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bjorn Borg Martina Navratlilova"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"According to Olympic rules, what number of feathers must a badminton bird (shuttlecock) have?", "answer":0, "answers":["Fourteen"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"According to rules of both sports, the top of which net is highest from the ground, Tennis or Table Tennis", "answer":0, "answers":["Tennis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Alan Shearer was the first player to score 200 Premiership goals. Who was the second?", "answer":0, "answers":["Andy Cole"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Alex Hurricane Higgins & Jimmy The Whirlwind White But Whats Ronnie O Sullivans Nickname", "answer":0, "answers":["Ronnie The Rocket O Sullivan"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Approximately how many dimples are in a golf ball?", "answer":0, "answers":["Between 300 and 500"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"AQOS is now the longest running sports quiz on TV when was it first broadcast? 1969, 1970, 1971,1972", "answer":0, "answers":["1970"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"As at August 2004, who is England's all time top goal scorer?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bobby Charlton"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"As We All Know David Beckham Now Plays For US Team LA Galaxy But Who Is The Coach For La Galaxy", "answer":0, "answers":["Ruud Gullit"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"As who is Cassius Clay now known?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mohammed Ali"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"At The 1976 Olympics, Only One Competitor Was Excused The Compulsory Sex Test. Who Was That Competitor?", "answer":0, "answers":["Princess Anne"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"At The Start Of The 2002/03 Season Who was the Premierships Highest Goal Scorer", "answer":0, "answers":["Alan Shearer"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"At what age can a player join the Seniors Golf Tour 45, 50 or 55?", "answer":0, "answers":["50"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"At what age did Will Carling first become England skipper?", "answer":0, "answers":["22"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"At Which Course Is The British Grand Prix Held?", "answer":0, "answers":["Silverstone"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"At Which Course Is The Derby Run Each Year?", "answer":0, "answers":["Epsom"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"At Which Event Has Steve Backley Won Olympic Bronze & Silver Medals", "answer":0, "answers":["Javelin"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"At Which Grand Prix Circuit Did Aryton Senna Lose His Life?", "answer":0, "answers":["San Marino , Italy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"At Which Ground Do Scotland Play Their Home International Rugby Union Matches", "answer":0, "answers":["Murrayfield"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"At Which Motor Racing Circuit Was Ayrton Senna Killed", "answer":0, "answers":["Imola"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"At Which Scottish Golf Venue Are The Eden Course & The Jubilee Course", "answer":0, "answers":["St Andrews"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"At Which Sport Did James Bond Play Auric Goldfinger Waging A Gold Bar On The Outcome?", "answer":0, "answers":["Golf"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"At which sport did Magic Johnson excel?", "answer":0, "answers":["Basketball"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"At Which Sport Might You See A Crucifix", "answer":0, "answers":["Gynmastics (The Rings)"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"At which sport was Fred Perry crowned world champion in 1929?", "answer":0, "answers":["Table Tennis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"At Which Sport Was Hungarian Victor Barna World Singles Champion 5 Times", "answer":0, "answers":["Table Tennis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"At Which Sporting Venue Are The Grace Gates", "answer":0, "answers":["Lords"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"At which sporting venue are the Grace Gates?", "answer":0, "answers":["Lord's"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"At which sporting venue can you visit the oldest sports museum n the world?", "answer":0, "answers":["Lord's ( MCC Museum )"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"At Which Sporting Venue Do Competitors Travel Down The Brabham Strait?", "answer":0, "answers":["Brands Hatch"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"At Which Sporting Venue Would You Find Melling Road?", "answer":0, "answers":["Aintree Race Course"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"At which venue did Steve Redgrave win his first gold?", "answer":0, "answers":["Los Angeles"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"At Which Venue Does The Us Open Tennis Tournament Take place", "answer":0, "answers":["Flushing Meadows"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Back in the 1890's which football club used to wear pink shirts? (Still In Premiership)", "answer":0, "answers":["Everton"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Baseball: The Atlanta ______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Braves"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Baseball: The Baltimore ________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Orioles"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Baseball: The Boston ______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Red Sox"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Baseball: The Chicago ______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cubs"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Baseball: The Cleveland ______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Indians"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Baseball: The Florida ______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Marlins"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Baseball: The Houston ______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Astros"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Baseball: The Kansas City ______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Royals"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Baseball: The Milwaukee ______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Brewers"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Baseball: The New York ______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mets"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Baseball: The Philadelphia ______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Phillies"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Baseball: The St. Louis ______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cardinals"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Baseball: The Texas ______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Rangers"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Baseball: The Toronto _________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Bluejays"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Basketball: The Boston ___________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Celtics"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Basketball: The Denver _________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Nuggets"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Basketball: The Denver ______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Nuggets"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Basketball: The Los Angeles _________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Lakers"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Basketball: The New York __________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Knicks"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Basketball: The Seattle ________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Supersonics"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Basketball: The Utah ________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Jazz"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Before Alex Ferguson Who Was Manager Of Manchester United", "answer":0, "answers":["Ron Atkinson (Red Ron)"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Between 1950 And 2000 Name Three Tennis Players Born in Germany That Won The Men's Singles Title At Wimbledon? (PFE)", "answer":0, "answers":["Boris Becker , John McEnroe & Michael Stich"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Between 1961 & 1990 a win in Formula One was worth how many points?", "answer":0, "answers":["Nine"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"California Dolls Is A Movie That Was Inspired By And Features Which Sport", "answer":0, "answers":["Wrestling"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"California Dolls Is An 80's Movie Comedy About Which Sport", "answer":0, "answers":["Wrestling"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Can you name 2 British golfers to win the US Masters in the 1990's?", "answer":0, "answers":["Nick Faldo & Ian Woosnam"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Canadian Ben Johnson Famously Lost His Olympic Title,World Record & Gold Medal By Failing A Drugs Test At The Summer Olympics But Where & When Did This Take Place ' Where (Country) & When (Year) ''", "answer":0, "answers":["1988, Seoul / Korea"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Colin Hendry left Blackburn in 1998 to join which Scottish Club?", "answer":0, "answers":["Rangers"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Colin McRae joined which rally team in 1991?", "answer":0, "answers":["Subaru"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Competitive Swimming Has 4 Events Butterfly, Breast Stroke, Back Stroke, & What Other", "answer":0, "answers":["Freestyle"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"David Campeze Was the Leading try Scorer for Which country", "answer":0, "answers":["Australia"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Did The Game Of Polo Originate In India, Persia, Or Argentina", "answer":0, "answers":["Persia (Iran)"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"During A Hockey Bully Off How Many Times Must Sticks Touch", "answer":0, "answers":["3 Times"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Dwight York & Jimmy Floyd Hasselbaink Were Two Foreign Players Who Were First To Score 100 Goals In the English Premiership Who Was The Third?", "answer":0, "answers":["Thierry Henry"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"England play their home rugby union matches at which venue?", "answer":0, "answers":["Twickenham"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"England Played Football At The Weekend Or Tried To But Only Managed A 0-0, Draw Who Did They Play Against", "answer":0, "answers":["Macedonia"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Euro 2008 Gets Underway Later This Year But Can You Tell Me Either Of The Two Host Countries PFE", "answer":0, "answers":["Austria & Switzerland"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Field of Dreams is a film about what?", "answer":0, "answers":["Baseball"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Fighting With Gloves Became Standard In 1867 After The Formulation Of Which Set Of Rules", "answer":0, "answers":["The Queensbury Rules"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Football: The Baltimore ________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Colts"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Football: The Buffalo _______.", "answer":0, "answers":["Bills"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Football: The Chicago ______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bears"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Football: The Cincinnati _________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Bengals"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Football: The Cleveland ________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Browns"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Football: The Dallas _________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Cowboys"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Football: The Dallas ______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cowboys"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Football: The Denver _________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Broncos"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Football: The Denver ____?", "answer":0, "answers":["Broncos"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Football: The Miami __________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Dolphins"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Football: The Minnesota _______.", "answer":0, "answers":["Vikings"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Football: The New Orleans __________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Saints"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Football: The Pittsburgh ______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Steelers"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Football: The San Diego ______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Chargers"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"Football: The Seattle _______.", "answer":0, "answers":["Seahawks"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"For Which Formula One Team Did Both Nigel Mansell & Damon Hill Drive", "answer":0, "answers":["Williams"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"For which International side did Shane Warne play Cricket?", "answer":0, "answers":["Australia"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"From which club did Manchester United sign Roy Keane?", "answer":0, "answers":["Nottingham Forest"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"From Which Country Do The Soccer Team Anderlecht Hail", "answer":0, "answers":["Belgium"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"SPORT_AND_LEISURE", "lang":"en", "tags":["SPORT_AND_LEISURE"], "question":"From Which Football Club Did Arsenal Sign Thierry Henry?", "answer":0, "answers":["Juventus"], "source":""}
]